

#### Rifki Kurniawan

Yogyakarta - Indonesia

I am a creative, dedicated, and detail-oriented UI/UX Designer with over 2 years of experience. Throughout my journey as a designer, I have developed skills in creating visually appealing and functional interfaces. I believe that good design can enhance user experience and provide effective solutions. I am committed to creating intuitive designs, with a focus on user satisfaction and alignment with business goals. I enjoy collaborating with teams, exploring new ideas, and continuously developing my skills in the design industry.

# **Experience**

# UI/UX Designer

PT. Anak Bangsa Cerdas Digital - Yogyakarta

Dec 2021 - Present

- Perform interface design for software, mobile applications and others.
- Responsible for designing an attractive display both in terms of shape, color and writing.
- · Research ideas and create design concepts.
- Redesign according to the client's wishes and adjust the layout, color scheme and shape of the buttons to make it easier for users.

#### **Content Creator**

G45 Ventures - Yogyakarta

Feb 2021 - May 2021

- Take photos of food, rooms, activities, more
- · Create website designs, feeds and stories for corporate platform
- Make youtube videos for company needs

### **Education**

#### **Bachelor Degree, Informatics**

Amikom University Of Yogyakarta - Yogyakarta

2019 - 2023

Learn and apply principles of computer science, software development, computer performance, UI/UX, design, and 2d & 3d animation.

#### Skill

- Understands design principles well
- Have more than 2 years experience as ui/ux designer
- · Has a good interest in art and design
- Has experience in photography
- Blends well in new environments
- Have problem solving skills
- · likes new things to learn

### **Contact**

(in

Rifki Kurniawan



rifki5073@gmail.com



0838-4043-5103



rifkurniawan\_

**Portfolio** 



Google Drive

